（轻音乐）
(gentle music)
因此，您在上一节中学习了 HTML 的基础知识。
So you learnt the basics of HTML in the last section.
所以现在是时候学习基础知识了
And so now it's time to learn the basics
网络的第二种语言，那就是 CSS。
of the second language of the web, and that is CSS.
现在，CSS 本质上就是为内容设置样式
Now, CSS is essentially all about styling the content
我们用 HTML 编写的。
that we write in HTML.
所以在本节中，我们将继续构建
And so in this section, we will keep building
我们的项目，基本上添加了一些视觉样式。
our project and basically add some visual styles to it.
我们还将学习一些理论概念
We will also learn some theoretical concepts
在 CSS 后面，
that are behind CSS,
以便您真正了解 CSS 的工作原理。
so that you actually understand how CSS works.
这真的很重要
And this is really important
因为那时，一旦你开始编写自己的代码，
because then, once you start writing your own code,
你会真正知道你在做什么。
you will actually know what you're doing.
所以我希望这一切听起来真的很令人兴奋，
So I hope all that sounds really exciting,
让我们开始吧。
and so let's get started.